Like, laugh at them.
Laugh at them.
I wish I had a hoodie on.
I mean, are we trying to play sorority sister
as this elected official?
I don't know, I was at a sorority over the weekend
over in Texas.
I felt like I was back at the sorority house,
except they had more sense.
Steven, quick response.
Well, we knew that her brain didn't work.
Now we know their eyes don't work.
So, I mean, she's a mess, right?
What a train wreck.
I think you should just get a hoodie.
You should just wear a hoodie from now on
and respond to her in a hoodie.
She'll be hoodie to hoodie.
Steven, thank you so much.
Yeah, go ahead.
I think the important point is that
every time she's on TV, Republican approval ratings go up,
Democrat approval ratings go down.
That lady is a walking nightmare.
And you're about, I know you for 20 years,
you're about five, 10, 11.
About 5'10", so 4'10", I don't know what you can say.
All right, Steven, thank you very much.
Hey, Sean Hannity here.
Hey, click here to subscribe to Fox News' YouTube page
and catch our hottest interviews
and most compelling analysis.
You will not get it anywhere else.